So thanks for coming by guys, we just wanted to bounce some ideas off of you about the
謝謝你們趕過來
wedding ceremony.
我們希望你們能幫我們 想一些婚禮上用的點子
What's the matter?
-怎麼了？你還好嗎？ -那只是因為…
Are you okay?
Yeah, it's just, you know.
你們怎麼知道？
Monica said weddings.
摩妮卡說了「婚禮」
So anyway, we thought that one of you could read something at the ceremony.
我們希望你們之中 有人能上台念些感性的文章
I would love to read a poem.
那是個很棒的故事吧？
Do you think you could get through a poem?
Yes, a short one.
Okay, so Ross will be doing the reading.
好的，到時候見，再見
Okay, yeah, I guess I could do that too.
好吧，我想我應該也能勝任
Two?
也能勝任？
Yeah, I kind of have something else planned for you guys.
我自己想了一個點子 來慶祝你們的婚禮
Do you mind telling us what it is?
-你能告訴我們是什麼點子嗎？ -抱歉
Sorry, I'm kind of keeping this one on the QT.
我想把它當成是高度機密
Well, whatever it is, I hope it involves winking.
不管你是指哪個，我希望會有眨眼睛
Hey!
-嗨 -嘿
So I just talked to one of the Duel writers today.
我跟DOOL的編劇談過…
What is Duel?
那是什麼聲音？
Days of our lives.
-什麼是DOOL？ -《我們的日子》
Anyway, you're not going to believe it, my character is coming out of his coma!
你們一定不相信 我演的角色就要醒過來了
Oh, that's great!
不，那是拉瓜迪亞機場
And not only that, I'm getting a new brain!
不只是那個，我會有個新腦子！
So great things are happening at work and in your personal life.
你的工作跟私生活 都有了很棒的進展
Wait, what do you mean you're getting a new brain?
你要換個新腦子？
Well, they're killing off one of the characters on the show and when she dies,
他們要踢走劇中一個角色…
her brain is being transplanted into my body!
將她的腦子移植到我的身體裡
What? A brain transplant?
什麼？腦部移植手術？
Yes, it's a highly controversial procedure.
It's ridiculous!
這太可笑了
Oh, I think it's ridiculous that you haven't had sex in three and a half months.
It's winter, there are fewer people on the street.
現在是冬天，街上的人少了很多
Who are they killing off?
他們要踢走誰？
Uh, Cecilia Monroe, she plays Jessica Lockhart.
西西雅夢露，她飾演潔西卡拉哈特
No!
不！
She's my favorite character on Duel!
她是我的室友瑞秋
Nice.
太棒了
She is so good at throwing drinks in people's faces,
她最擅長將飲料潑到別人臉上
I mean, I don't think I've ever seen her finish a beverage.
我從來沒看過她喝完一杯飲料
And the way she slaps people all the time, wouldn't you love to do that just once?
還有她打人巴掌的樣子 你不想那麼做嗎？
Don't do it!
別那麼做
Cecilia Monroe, man, what a great actress.
Oh, tell me about it. And she's been on the show forever.
她參與這齣戲的演出很久了
It's going to be really hard to fill her shoes.
要代替她一定很難
Yeah, yeah, well, help me out here.
你得幫幫我
When you come out of the brain transplant,
當你做過腦部移植手術後…
you are going to be her?
你要變成她？
Yes, but in Drake Ramore's body.
對，她被困在德瑞克的身體裡
Why is it so hard for you to get? I thought you were a scientist.
你為什麼就是搞不懂？ 我還以為你是科學家
I'll be there for you.
夢露小姐…喔，你真的那麼做了
When it hasn't been your day, week, month, even now, year.
But I'll be there for you.
你知道他來的時候我會在這裡
Because you're there for me too.
你說的對，他們要將我踢出這齣戲
Great, so that guy there, straight or gay?
是異性戀還是同性戀？
Well, I'd have to say gay.
Yeah, why?
好的
Mainly because he's kissing that other guy.
我注意到了，那是因為她 充滿了熱情嗎？
Oh, no, not that guy there. That guy right there.
瑞秋，那邊那個男的…
Oh.
Oh, yeah, he's too cute to be straight.
他太帥了，不可能是異性戀
Oh, knockers will help us figure it out.
大波霸小姐會幫我們查個清楚
All right, straight.
好了，他是異性戀
And not subtle.
而且一眼就看得出來
Oh, he left his cell phone.
他忘了拿手機
Oh, well, we could hand it to Gunther and he'll put it in Lost and Found.
我們得把它交給阿甘 放在失物招領處
Or we could use it to call China, see how those guys are doing.
或是用它打電話到中國 看看那些人在做什麼
What if he calls his own cell phone to find out who found it,
如果他打電話來找手機 我接了電話…
and I answer and we start talking, and we fell in love?
我們開始聊天，之後墜入愛河呢？
I mean, wouldn't that be amazing?
那是個很棒的故事吧？
Wouldn't that be a great story?
Kind of like a fairy tale for the digital age.
就像是數位時代的童話故事
Yeah, that does sound great.
對，我們應該…
I'm going to get the phone.
那麼由我來把手機交給他
What? Wait, why? Why do you get the story?
什麼？等一下 為什麼你會成為故事的女主角？
I don't know, I haven't been out on a date in so long.
我已經很久沒有約會了
Phoebe, you had a date three days ago.
菲比，三天前你才約過會
That wasn't a date, that was just friends getting together.
那不是約會，那只是 朋友聚會，然後做愛
Having sex.
Okay, see, I get the phone.
好吧，我去拿手機
No, wait, no, wait, you just broke up with Tag a week ago.
不行，一星期前你才跟泰格分手
Yeah, and until now, I didn't think I would love again.
對，直到現在，我才明白 我能再愛一次
Nice try.
-說的好 -等一下
Well, hey, wait, wait, how do we fairly decide who gets the phone?
我們該怎麼公平地決定 誰能拿走手機呢？
I don't know.
我不知道
Well, um, maybe we could, uh...
或許我們可以…
Ha-ha, too slow! Ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha!
你動作太慢了！
Ha-ha! Too cocky!
你太自大了
I'm going to keep dating him, Mother, and there's nothing you can do about it.
媽媽嗎？
Oh, yes, there is.
不，我管得了
What are you going to do, kill him? Like you did Charles?
你打算怎麼做？殺了他嗎？ 就像你殺了查爾斯？
That was an accident.
那是鐵證
And so were you.
你是誰？
Well, at least I'm not a murderer.
Oh, my baby!
我的寶貝
That was a great scene.
那是個很棒的故事吧？
And that slap looked so real. How do you do that?
你演得太好了，剛剛那一巴掌 很逼真，你怎麼辦到的？
Oh, just years of experience.
-那只是多年的經驗 -快拿冰塊過來給我
Can I get some ice here?
Well, anyway, I just wanted to say how wonderful I think you are.
我只想說我覺得你的演技很棒
You're not the fan who's dying, are you?
你該不會是那個快死掉的影迷吧？
What?
什麼？
I was supposed to meet and hug a fan who's dying,
but that's not supposed to be until later.
No, no, I'm Joey Tribbiani.
We did a scene together yesterday.
我是喬伊崔比亞尼 昨天我們合拍過一場戲
I'm the guy in the coma.
-我就是那個昏迷的人 -那是真人？
Oh, that was a real person?
Anyway, I just wanted to say that
我只想說我覺得你的演技很棒
since I'm getting your brain when you leave the show,
因為你離開後我要移植你的腦子…
I was wondering if there's any tips you could give me.
我在想如果…
I'm leaving the show?
-我要離開？ -為什麼？你聽到了什麼？
I don't know. Why? Did you hear something?
我不知道
Who told you that?
是誰告訴你的？
One of the writers.
-編劇之一 -哪個編劇？是禿頭佬還是高個子？
Which writer? Was it bald or was it tall?
You know what? It doesn't matter.
那不重要，因為那不是真的
Because it is not true.
Okay.
好吧
And if it were true?
如果那是真的 你竟然敢來叫我教你…
How dare you come to me and ask me for tips
about a character that I've been playing for 20 years.
該如何飾演我演了二十年的角色
I'll give you a tip.
好吧，我把他讓給你
Miss Monroe.
夢露小姐…喔，你真的那麼做了
Oh, there you go.
No, Phoebe, you cannot get the phone that way.
-菲比，你不能… -我在講電話
That's not fair.
她是我的室友瑞秋
Okay, look, I have an idea.
好吧，聽著，我有個點子
Why don't we see what kind of numbers
我們為什麼不看看 他的速撥鍵記錄了哪些電話號碼…
he has on his speed dial?
And then from that, we can tell
就是這樣了
who has more in common with him,
跟他有最多共通點的人 就可以把手機拿走
and then whoever does gets the phone.
Or we can decide by whoever's name
我們該怎麼公平地決定 誰能拿走手機呢？
is closer to the phone,
那麼由我來把手機交給他
I don't think so.
我可不那麼認為
Fine, all right.
-好吧 -好吧
But I bet you'd be singing a different tune
但現在…現在時機不一樣了
if we were fighting over a ratchet.
All right.
好吧
First name on the speed dial is Mom.
速撥鍵的第一個名字是「媽媽」
Oh, I lost my mom to suicide.
喔，我媽媽自殺死了
Okay, no way.
-我的天啊 -什麼？
You cannot use that to get the cute guy
不行，你不能利用那一點 搶走帥哥跟最後一塊藍莓鬆餅
and the last blueberry muffin.
Did I use that already today? I'm sorry.
今天我已經用過那個借口了？對不起
Okay.
好吧
Well, now, see, this isn't telling us
你們都知道這首歌，一起唱吧
anything.
不，謝謝，我不喜歡蘇格蘭的東西
Joe, Carlos,
班，卡洛斯，大衛…
yoga, Ben...
Wait, yoga, I do yoga. That's one for me.
什麼？等一下 為什麼你會成為故事的女主角？
Oh, all right. Oh, so close.
好吧
If only it said yogurt.
Ooh, Peter Luger.
That's a steakhouse.
她是我的室友瑞秋
Okay, fine, meat-eater, fine.
怎麼了？笛娜
That's one for you.
-那真的是太棒了 -哇，喬伊
Oh, I win.
我贏了，他在速撥鍵裡記下了巴尼斯
He's got Barney's on his speed dial.
So you don't know that it's Barney's the store.
你不知道他指的是不是巴尼斯服飾店
That could be, you know, his friend's house
那可能是他朋友家或是酒吧的電話…
or a bar.
我的寶貝
Who has Barney's the store on their speed dial?
誰會把巴尼斯服飾店的電話 記錄成速撥鍵？
His new girlfriend.
他的新女朋友
What is that?
那是什麼聲音？
I think it's the dying cat parade.
我想是快死掉的貓在舉行遊行
Sounds like it's coming from across the street.
聽起來是從對街傳來的
Oh, my God.
我的天啊
What?
什麼？
You know the thing that Ross was going to do at our wedding?
還記得羅斯說他要在 婚禮上給我們驚喜嗎？
He was hanging out with me yesterday and he turned to me and he said,
他跟我出去混時說： 「你有蘇格蘭的血統吧？」
You're half Scottish, right?
No!
不！
No, there is no way
不，不可能，不可能是羅斯
it cannot be Ross.
Unbelievable.
不可思議，為什麼你有蘇格蘭血統？
Why is your family Scottish?
Why is your family Ross?
為什麼羅斯是你哥哥？
He cannot play our wedding.
他不能在婚禮上演奏 大家都會跑光的
I mean, everyone will leave.
所有事物跟所有人
It'll be like when he rapped at my bat mitzvah.
Look, we can't just tell him no, okay?
-不會 -好吧
He's probably been practicing forever.
她參與這齣戲的演出很久了
He'll be crushed.
你得幫幫我
Well, maybe there's some way we can tell him without hurting his feelings.
I mean, come on.
我是說那只是噪音！
That is just noise.
It's not even a song.
那根本不算是歌
Listen very carefully.
等一下，如果你仔細聽…
I think
我只想說我覺得你的演技很棒
it's celebration by calling the gang.
我想它是庫爾 與夥伴合唱團唱的《慶祝》
Hi, Pheebs.
-嗨 -嘿
How are you?
你是誰？
Remember when we were in the coffee house
還記得我們在咖啡廳時…
we decided that I was going to keep the cute guy's cell phone?
我們決定我可以 拿走那個帥哥的手機嗎？
Yeah.
好的
And remember how I said I was going to keep it in my purse
我們決定我可以 拿走那個帥哥的手機嗎？
so that if it rang, I could just pick it up?
我要把它放在我的皮包裡 如果它響了，我就能立刻接聽？
Yeah.
好的
And then do you remember going into my purse
你還記得你從我的皮包 把手機偷走了嗎？
and stealing the phone?
Now you lost me.
我聽不懂你在說什麼
You stole the phone.
-你偷走了手機 -不，我沒有
No, I didn't.
No? So you're saying that if I called it,
如果我撥號過去它不會響嗎？
it wouldn't ring?
Nope.
不！
Okay, but while you dial, let me show you the features
既然你要撥號了，我要讓你看看 我剛買的響鈴皮包
of my new ringing handbag.
Hmm.
Oh, it does work.
喔，它真的有用
Phoebe, that is a different phone.
-菲比 -那是另一隻手機
Oh, is it?
是嗎？喂，對，你好，瑞秋在嗎？
Uh, hello?
-嗨 -嘿
Yes, hi. Is Rachel there?
是嗎？喂，對，你好，瑞秋在嗎？
Yes, she is. Just one moment, please.
她在，請稍等，是找我的！
It's for me.
That is damning evidence.
那是鐵證
Oh, my God.
我的天啊
I bet that's him.
我的天啊，我敢說是他打來的
My digital fairy tale is about to begin.
我的數位童話故事就要開始了
I wonder how I should be.
-那真的是太棒了 -哇，喬伊
Should I be, uh, hello?
我的天啊，我敢說是他打來的
Or should I be hi?
Would you stop doing that?
你能不能別再那麼做了？
Hello?
Yes, I'm the one who found your phone.
喂，對，我就是撿到你手機的人
Phoebe, you can't shut me on a call.
-菲比，你不能… -我在講電話
Hello?
Um, well, yeah, I mean, you could pick it up
對，今晚你能過來拿，就八點半吧？
tonight, say, 8.30
是異性戀還是同性戀？
at my apartment.
到我家來
It's, um,
這太可笑了
it's 5 Morton Street, apartment 14.
摩頓街五號，十四號房
And then maybe, you know,
或許之後我們可以去吃點東西
after we could grab a bite to eat or whatever.
Okay.
好吧
Okay, I'll see you then. Bye.
好的，到時候見，再見
You do know that I will be here when he comes over.
你知道他來的時候我會在這裡
Oh, and how will you know
你們怎麼知道？
what time to come over?
你怎麼知道他什麼時候會來？
You just said it.
你剛剛說出來了
Oh.
Okay, well, I was
好吧，聽著，我有個點子
kind of hoping that I would just
我自己想了一個點子 來慶祝你們的婚禮
be alone, you know, to
你們怎麼知道？
think about my mom
喔，我媽媽自殺死了
and her suicide. Oh, Phoebe!
What? That's the first time today. Oh!
-怎麼了？你還好嗎？ -那只是因為…
So, you like the nachos, huh?
我的天啊，我敢說是他打來的
Myself, I'm partial. I'm 16.
See you in 2003.
You're absolutely right. They are writing me out
你說的對，他們要將我踢出這齣戲
of the show. They don't know exactly when
他們還沒有決定 什麼時候，但應該很快…
it's going to happen, but apparently it's going to be very
這有點奇怪，但已經好多了
soon, and then that's it.
就是這樣了
I'm so sorry.
-我真的很抱歉 -不
Look, if it was up to me, you would never leave the show.
我真的很抱歉，如果我可以決定 你永遠都不會離開這齣戲
Yeah, thanks. No, I mean it.
-謝謝你 -我是認真的
I can't believe they would do this to you
我不敢相信他們會對你這麼做 還有你的影迷
and to your fans.
I mean, they're going to be devastated, heartbroken.
他們一定會崩潰傷心 他們是那麼地愛你
They love you so much.
Oh, you're right.
你說的對
Thank you.
謝謝
What's your name again?
你說你叫什麼名字？
Joey. Joey, well, thank you.
謝謝
That is so sweet.
那真的太貼心了
Excuse me.
是因為…
It wasn't my decision.
我在想如果…
I'm having a conversation here.
You were saying?
你才華洋溢
Look, the only
你擁有這個房間
reason that I came up to you
聽著，之前我會來找你...
before is because
是因為…
well, I'm really nervous
因為要飾演你我真的很緊張
about being you.
You know, if you could help me capture
請你幫我抓住角色的精髓
the essence of the character.
You know, help me keep Jessica alive.
幫助我讓潔西卡 繼續活下去，可以嗎？
Please.
All right, Joey.
好吧
I will help you.
好吧，喬伊，我會幫你
Not because I owe it to this stupid show.
不是因為我對這出蠢戲有虧欠…
But because
而是因為我虧欠潔西卡
I owe it to Jessica.
Well, that's great.
不，那是拉瓜迪亞機場
Oh, thank you so much.
謝謝
You're so welcome.
-那真的是太棒了，謝謝你 -別客氣
Hey, now, I've been watching some tapes.
我一直在觀摩錄影帶 你覺得這招如何？
How's this?
Jessica Lockhart will never step foot in this place again.
潔西卡拉哈特 永遠都不會再踏入這裡！
Never!
永遠都不會！
Is that supposed to be me?
是我
Yeah.
好的
Well, but
Jessica doesn't have an English accent.
但潔西卡沒有英國腔
I can do an English accent?
我有英國腔？
That baby's going
我要把這點寫在我的履歷表裡
on my resume.
Well, I feel like a snack.
我想吃點點心
Do you want some shortbread?
你要吃點脆餅嗎？ 它是你故鄉蘇格蘭的點心
It's Scottish, like you are.
Oh, no thanks.
不，謝謝，我不喜歡蘇格蘭的東西
I don't like anything from my Scottish
heritage.
不，謝謝，我不喜歡蘇格蘭的東西
What?
什麼？
Well, it's just my entire family
因為我的家族被趕出蘇格蘭…
was run out of Scotland by
Vikings.
是維京人幹的
Anyway, lots of bad memories.
Well, it sounds to me like
我想吃點點心
your family's ready to
聽起來你家人 準備要恢復蘇格蘭傳統
rediscover its Scottish roots.
No.
不！
No, no, they're not.
一，二，三，四！
They're still very angry.
But, you know, Chandler's also
你們都知道這首歌，一起唱吧
half Swedish. You know what the Swedish
你怎麼知道他什麼時候會來？
people are famous for?
一，二，三，四！
Sitting down and being quiet.
我有英國腔？
Yeah, yeah, but
對，我們應該…
the Scottish history is so much...
You cannot play bagpipes at the wedding.
你不能在婚禮上吹風笛！
How did you know about that?
你們怎麼知道？
We heard you play all the way from your apartment.
-我們聽到你在家裡吹風笛 -是你們去報警的？
Were you the ones who called the cops?
That's not really important right now.
現在那真的不重要
What is important is
重要的是，我們謝謝你的好意…
while we appreciate the gesture,
we just don't feel that bagpipes
我們只是覺得 我們的婚禮上不適合吹風笛
are appropriate for
our wedding. Why not?
Because we hate them.
-為什麼？ -因為我們討厭風笛
Come on, that's not fair.
我是說那只是噪音！
You haven't even heard me play.
你要變成她？
We have heard you play.
No, you've heard me practice.
你要換個新腦子？
Okay, just give me a chance to
不，等一下，還有一件事
perform for you, and then decide
給我機會為你們表演 再做最後的決定
whatever you want. And I'm not
-菲比，你不能… -我在講電話
going to tell you what song I'm going to play either,
我也不會告訴你們 我要吹哪首曲子
but let's just say
就說當表演結束後…
when it's over, I'll bet there'll be
我們一定會慶祝一下
a wee bit-o celebration.
So, the essence
不，我管得了
of the character is rooted
這個角色的精髓源自於她的自信
in her confidence.
So when Jessica enters a room
譬如說，當潔西卡走進一個房間時…
for instance, she owns
everything and
她擁有那個房間裡…
every person in that room.
所有事物跟所有人
You try.
-你來試試看 -好吧
Okay.
好吧
Alright!
No,
不！
he already knows that he owns
-我真的很抱歉 -不
everything in the room. He's not finding it out
我在跟他約會，你管不了
for the first time. So
try it again.
再試一次，他擁有它 他擁有這個房間
Okay, okay.
好的，到時候見，再見
Right. He's not angry
那根本不算是歌
at the room either.
怎麼了？笛娜
Try it again. He owns it.
再試一次，他擁有它 他擁有這個房間
He owns the room. It is his.
你擁有這個房間
He owns, owns,
這是他的，他擁有 這個房間！他擁有它！
owns the room! He owns it!
Alright, it's a little weird, but
這有點奇怪，但已經好多了
it's getting better.
Oh,
I'm going to miss this woman so much.
我一定會很想念這個女人 我不知道我該怎麼辦
I don't know what I'm going to do. I mean, it's been
我不知道
20 years of my life.
我演這齣戲二十年了
Hey, hey, maybe,
-嘿 -嘿
maybe this is a good thing.
或許這是件好事
You know, it'll give you a chance to
好的，到時候見，再見
shake things up, play different characters.
它給你機會做改變 扮演不一樣的角色
You're so talented.
你才華洋溢
I am, I am, but
I don't know, you know,
我不知道
an actor of a certain age,
it's not that easy.
那根本不算是歌
Hey, that's not true.
就是這樣了
Look at, uh,
譬如說呢？
look at Angelina Jolie.
I probably should have just
left years ago
或許我該在幾年前離開 那時很多人要我接戲…
when the offers were pouring in, but,
you know, I just get so comfy here, and
但我在這裡過得太舒服…
I turned down
我拒絕了一些大好機會
some amazing work.
Like what?
譬如說呢？
Well, let's just say, if I left 15 years
喔，就說如果我在十五年前離開…
ago, the landscape
of Mexican cinema
現在的墨西哥影壇會完全不一樣
would be very different today.
Wow.
哇
But,
卡！
well, now,
但現在…現在時機不一樣了
now's a different time for me.
Oh, hey, come on.
嘿，別這樣
Don't, uh, don't do this.
Look, let me tell you something,
聽我說句話，好嗎？
okay? Now, when I watch you
好吧，聽著，我有個點子
do a scene, I'm thinking, boy, she,
當我看到你演戲時 我想「天啊，她是個很棒的演員」
she is a great actress.
But, but, I'm also
thinking she is hot.
但我也會想「她好辣」
You think I'm hot?
你覺得我很辣？
You own the room.
你擁有這個房間
We should probably
或許我們應該…
get, get, uh...
Oh, yeah, yeah, we should get...
對，我們應該…
So, when Jessica
譬如說，當潔西卡走進一個房間時…
kisses a man,
當潔西卡吻男人時…
she
沒錯
usually puts, um,
她通常會把…
both her hands on the
雙手放在那個男人臉上
man's face.
Yeah, yeah, I noticed that.
對，我們應該…
Is that because she's so passionate?
我注意到了，那是因為她 充滿了熱情嗎？
No, it's because that way the camera only sees her.
不，那是因為 那樣子攝影機只能拍到她
You want to try it?
你想試試看嗎？
Yeah,
好的
okay.
好吧
That was good.
太棒了，真的很不錯
That was really good.
But I, I think that maybe your hands
但我想你手的位置不對 它們應該…
are just a little off. They should be maybe
like, right, like...
譬如說呢？
Hey, hey!
-嘿 -嘿
Who is it?
是誰？
Hi, it's Tom.
喔，它真的有用
I'm here to pick up the phone.
我是湯姆，我來拿手機的
Well,
why do you get to answer the door?
為什麼要由你去開門？
Well, why shouldn't I?
Because it's my apartment.
-為什麼不行？ -因為這裡是我家
Well, then I get to give him the cell phone.
那麼由我來把手機交給他
Okay, alright. Good luck explaining all the calls
祝你好運
to China.
好吧，希望你能好好 跟他解釋那些打到中國的電話
Hi.
嗨
Well, how long were we arguing for?
我們爭執了多久？
Um, you're not the man
你不是那個忘了拿手機的人
who left the cell phone.
他忘了拿手機
No, that's my assistant.
-對，他是我的助理 -他會來嗎？
Is he coming?
Um, no.
不！
Could you, could you, um, give us one second?
-你能讓我們談一下嗎？ -沒問題
Sure. We'll be right back, sir.
我們馬上回來
Well, what do we do?
-我們該怎麼辦？ -我不知道
I don't know.
我不知道
Can you believe this?
你能相信嗎？
We're waiting for a hot guy and then an even hotter
我們在等一個帥哥 結果來了一個超級大帥哥
one shows up.
I know.
我知道
What?
什麼？
I mean, they just don't make them
我是說那只是噪音！
like that anymore, do they?
No, no, they do,
一，二，三，四！
but you just have to wait.
你剛剛說出來了
Rachel, listen, I mean,
瑞秋，聽我說…
if you
等一下，如果你仔細聽…
let me have him, then I will
如果你能把他讓給我 我真的欠你一個大人情
really owe you one.
Alright.
好吧
Alright, Phoebe, I will let you have him,
好吧，我把他讓給你
but you owe me. You owe me big.
但你欠我一個大人情
Yeah.
好的
You're such a great friend.
你才華洋溢
So, which one of you lovely ladies
哪一位漂亮的小姐要陪我去吃晚餐？
am I going to take to dinner, huh?
你要變成她？
Oh, that'd be me.
是我
Sir.
沒錯
Thank you.
謝謝
Well, you
你的確擁有那個房間
certainly own that room.
Actually, I rent the whole place
事實上我租下整間公寓 我剛瞭解你的意思，謝謝誇獎
and I just got what you meant.
我剛瞭解你的意思，那…
Thank you.
謝謝
Hi. Hey.
-嗨 -嘿
Oh, my God.
我的天啊
Oh, Jessica Lockhart!
潔西卡拉哈特！在我家裡面！
In my apartment!
I am such a huge
我是你的頭號大影迷 我是你的頭號大影迷
fan. I am such a huge fan.
Well, it's nice to know that you work...
很高興能知道…
Monica! Monica!
摩妮卡！
That, uh, that's my
那是什麼聲音？
roommate, Rachel.
她是我的室友瑞秋
Oh, that explains all the women's underwear.
難怪你家會有女人內衣
Sure.
沒錯
Oh, my God!
我的天啊
It's true!
我的天啊，是真的！
Oh, my God. You are so
我的天啊
amazing.
我拒絕了一些大好機會
Oh, my God. Can I just ask you to do me
我的天啊
just one favor?
我的天啊，我能請你幫我一個忙嗎？
Certainly.
當然可以
Would you slap me? Would you slap me right here in the face?
你能打我一巴掌嗎？
I'd love to, but my lawyer said
我很願意，但我的律師說 我不能再那麼做了
I can't do that anymore.
You seem really, really
nice. Okay. Bye-bye.
-不會 -好吧
I mean, not fake at all
like most famous people.
All right. Here we go.
好了，我們走吧
Just one more thing.
不，等一下，還有一件事
You're a stupid bitch.
-你是個笨女人 -我真的不能打你巴掌
I really can't slap you.
You are so beautiful.
你才華洋溢
I'm so nice to meet you.
很高興能知道…
My God, you're great.
-我的天啊，你太棒了 -謝謝你們過來
Hey, just stopping by.
I am so sorry.
-我真的很抱歉 -不
Oh, no, no, no, no, no.
我聽不懂你在說什麼
Being adored, I'm used to it. Don't worry about it.
我習慣被影迷包圍，別擔心
Oh, my God. What?
-我的天啊 -什麼？
They sent me today's script.
他們寄了今天的劇本來給我 他們從來沒有寄劇本給過我
They never send me the script. They don't.
Well, no, I'm just in a coma.
-是嗎？ -我一直都昏迷不醒
This must mean I have lines.
這代表我有台詞了
Oh.
How does it happen?
我是怎麼死的？
You get thrown from a horse
你摔下馬，然後撞到電籬笆
into an electric fence.
What? Jessica hates horses.
什麼？潔西卡討厭馬
Yeah, well, I'm guessing after this,
好吧，我想我應該也能勝任
she's not gonna be crazy about electricity, either.
經過這件事，她也不會喜歡電
Now, remember, you have to imagine
請記住 我還在學吹風笛
me in a kilt.
Ha.
什麼？
I can imagine you in a short,
plaid skirt and knee socks.
You want to start telling secrets?
你想試試看嗎？
No.
不！
Now, um, remember,
請記住 我還在學吹風笛
I'm still learning.
Okay.
好吧
One, two, three, four.
一，二，三，四！
You know the song. Sing along.
你們都知道這首歌，一起唱吧
So?
怎麼樣？
No.
不！
Loosening the saddle on Mother's horse
在媽媽的馬鞍上動手腳 是個超級好點子，佛萊德克
was brilliant, Frederick.
And the electric fence, inspired.
電籬笆那個點子太妙了
Thank you, sweetheart.
謝謝你，親愛的
I can't believe she's
我不敢相信她真的死了
really gone.
Look around you. All of this is
看看你的四周，一切都是你的
ours.
I don't think so.
我可不那麼認為
Who are you?
你是誰？
What's the matter, Dina?
怎麼了？笛娜
Don't you recognize your own
你不認得你自己的…
mother?
媽媽嗎？
That was great, everybody. Thank you.
卡！大家都演得很好，謝謝
That was so wonderful.
那真的是太棒了
Oh, I think that
那是什麼聲音？
you're a better Jessica than I ever was.
我想你比我更適合演潔西卡
Oh, no.
不！
Of course not, but you were very good.
-喔，不 -當然不是，但你真的很棒
Thanks.
謝謝
And guess what? Good news. I got another job.
好消息，我找到新工作了
Great. Hey, all right.
好吧
What is it? A film in
那是什麼聲音？
Guadalajara.
我要到瓜達拉哈拉拍電影
The airport?
你是指那個機場？
No, that's LaGuardia.
不，那是拉瓜迪亞機場
This is Mexico.
-我要去墨西哥 -哇
Oh, wow. How long
我聽不懂你在說什麼
will you be gone?
你會去多久？
Eight months.
八個月
That's a really long time.
-那真的很久 -對，但你可以來看我
Yeah, but you could come and visit me.
I bet that you could
或許我們可以…
own a few places down there.
我敢說你能在那裡擁有幾個地方
You know,
那不重要，因為那不是真的
I tell you, I should probably buy a place
你知道的，或許我該先在紐約買房子
in the city first.
And I just got what you meant.
我剛瞭解你的意思，那…
I'll tell you, that's a tricky one.
-那真的有難度 -真的很難
That's a tricky one.
Well,
Joe, I really want to thank you.
謝謝
Well, you made
是誰告訴你的？
a very difficult time for me,
但現在…現在時機不一樣了
a little less painful.
Good luck.
祝你好運
You too.
你也是
you